Hello hello everyone if you are
in your twenties or late twenties then I am going to
tell you some such tips in this video about options. Everyone wants to earn money but no
one wants to know about money.
Select options like
stocks, mutual funds, real estate, gold
digger, Akhilesh will open it in this video.
Now stay tuned till the end so that
you get this point.
Everyone wants financial freedom but pension, education is
not available in my school. Then
what option can we take, let's
invest in this box, let's take
some tips on unwanted
investment. So for people
starting out, I
want to tell you about some such investment options
which turned out to be manufactured, which
we should not take, which we have to take.
Ladies taking loans on these loans are
available these days in large numbers. There are two
types of loans, generally Girnar loan, Uloom loan, I want to improve our situation.
Next in line for education or F-35,
but for that we need a loan.  By now I will take
somewhere 1MB one bill white Kishanlal
all types of education loan in this good time to
develop now on bread or this
platform loan refund it 19 sexual
matters like you take a loan to buy your mobile
you know this to buy your bike your dream bike you
take a loan to buy your house
you take a loan for 299 to buy voltage and hair do
not need a house that is
not for you and stay away from such people
but things which will avoid taking
best investment discussions like real
estate real estate for me is the best
why I will recommend you for a minute if
you take this house minimum total
box equipment happened in 10 2010 also cancelled
so in a year it happened almost ₹50 you will
add your decision which principal amount return online minimum 2225 and after that the
said decision will be made papa tells me take it
son return home you will be successful big
extra definitely now hydration is society
that dam you some good  I will invest
in replacing it which will give you
20% of your return and you will also buy a house,
quarter in the middle of the house,
buying records and maintenance costs and
my voice is torture, one more I did
not show today, a real story of
investing in gold which is in liquid
notice board and happened in the early twenties
this year third option third option which was till now
land is
133 invest in gold I am a golden
heater of gold investment is a very big
category why we have to buy shell then there are
Angol paste then like
meeting chances to make gold golon Baikunth Chaudas
prohibition gold funny this year investment because
subscribe to this then your next
15 years are going to be in effort
apart from this I give you a best
option
I will drop these in the beginning Guru your lips
are very much there you can invest in gold
without GST without making
charges every person friends it will not be like this no
one can steal gold only other
things you collect diet is your
Monthly expense or monthly expense is basically
what you spend on food on a daily basis.
Time is the gender test. These are the
symptoms shown on your delete clothing.
Try them. Om Need
Yadav and Smith will launch the first edition.
In this, taking flower button 365 is not healthy.
Second, real estate investment. Third,
gold investment. Fourth, this difference is all done
by Rashmi. Now let's go to five
such good investments which you should make
today. Early is possible which people get in 2015.
In this, third, performance is
a sequence. Life from Lord is higher
risk, low quality and is liquid.
And posting Laxman option is your life
term plan. Life in the creative is doing nonsense.
Life term plan. This tree minister is
₹500 to bank Nifty 6300. I am ₹5 duty
minister. You will do classified and you will get ID and
a natural melanin which will do Word 2003.
NDA UPA 1.25 1.20 if you 2000  1.22
that if you will do 60 lakhs or
even in favor of the same file behind you if Fortis will
do 60 lakhs then the difficulty will reduce if you want to
start then take a little time back to
life insurance necklace HDFC AB and The
Bank second best option for health
insurance
that now there is no need to tell anyone what happened last date
health
insurance point what am I saying in this that
all business benefits only when that
help mix is ​​kept for long term
two example was and to-do list does
not subscribe
playlist in love story it would feel if you
take out 36 and work in office 15 lakhs
for health insurance 100 feet what is a
83488 Ishq Khuda Haldi Suthra against
best option that you set to take health insurance
but since last year
I have destroyed the trust in it
situated insurance for you for this proposal
unit secondary school bond is a bond
third related songs and most important
mutual funds  I
will find all the subjects to market risks,
these are the dialogues, listen to your bytes, mutual
funds validation for 20, you should
not waste much time, do not waste your time, do not waste your time,
mutual funds, mom dad song
reminder, you can record also the amount,
tell me the timetable of the punch below, please do
n't like champion 231, alkaline, you can
take princess cake, you can
take lecture Anil Bhai, how can I invest, friend, you can
like this, cross the
mall, this is the last and points, our
mode setting, stop dance,
dance practice, all the times, different
meters for the missions were cancelled, they will do
Mexico, Mexico and
investment and the most hot investment
of which people are talking in the stock
market, it is very risky, I do
not understand the stock market, if I do
not understand then I cannot understand how to earn money,
yes, it is very risky in the stock market,
so you should listen to the market,
salute to these, a urologist from Technical Analysis and
Company
invests in stocks, this knowledge makes the
best and do not waste time on pornographic video clips
Information but you will get a little return
Jhansi how much more mutual funds can be done to
all 72800 2% other car
ownership for you Nippon has given 2% this year
all mutual funds have given
Sonu Nigam a second beard blue chip has
given investment in terms of more than twenty
six point if you had invested thousand above ok you
remain worried 100
pieces this year there are some stocks which have
1000 position from tourist places
symptoms diskpart you will have to do a little research for
sure mortal videos for sure
you will tell me how to calculate stocks how to
calculate fixed and which stocks should be taken
I will tell you in the next videos they do
obscene acts balance 800 all
sorts of broking firms fixed and
floating has direct investment
destination to b c&c and most recent
options investment currency friend what are you
saying in India then
cryptocurrency band cryptocurrency has to be done in
these pocket sets Amazon accepts cryptocurrency
now how many people use Amazon  Please
comment and tell me how many people knew that crypto
currency is accepted please select
for any third neuron there but this
cryptocurrency transaction has been done on Amazon
Alibaba other websites also in the
form of alum dam but management
latest soul from switch of India if
you want to invest so this mask
bitcoin what is bitcoin price
a bit coin 600 piece today data is active
Maithili 40 approximately to flex
bitcoin mostly screen system had the
right to transaction in it you
can invest in bitcoin from that 34 bank gold
coins which other is most scary office
365 has to increase the risk then this is the best
option for him for his life in the second
health insurance plan in these mutual
funds for this talk phase crypto currency ne
sub investment ke details hinday hai
if you want to tell me in the comment
no investment I am commenting to you
Vikas I have already invested this 500 something then the
latest collection is left
yesterday I have applied for next
week  His video is also out today and his
investment details or if you need help with this time, if you
need assignment comments, you will have to do manabe
or if you need debit details again, then
write and tell me in the comments and I will
give you a video camera, yes I am making a new video
and that is why everyone has to do the fairness adjective,
why do we hesitate in buying a spacecraft, cooking gesture
investment is very common, chili peas, everyone
knows about it but not everyone does it,
learn to invest smartly and
invest it as soon as possible, this is
130, in the next video I will be mixing you,
how will you invest in these five and
your salary and your income or your
pocket money, now as you invest in it, I will
tell you in the next video,
thank you for the next video,
stay in the video till the end, do you
invest in stocks, tell me by
writing in the comments, do you invest or
not, tell me this and if you
invest in affairs, tell me by writing in the comments,
I was helping you, you also could
not get free finance, thank you
for watching the video till the end  Please subscribe
my channel and if
you found even one new topic in this entire video,
please share it so that other
people can do illegal and safe investment.
I have no benefit in this,
just press the stop button and go.